We did our best
Most of the toxins have been cleared from the stomach
But the patient is elderly
He's in poor health
As for when he'll wake up
It's hard to say
Future medical costs will be high
Does the patient have any other children
Where is Daniel
I don't know
Since the accident
He hasn't shown up once
Is he even human
His parents even risked their lives for him
Yet he won't even show his face at the hospital
We shouldn't have given him that money
I've already had the bank recover that two million
Doctor, regardless of the cost
We want they treated
Sir, your card has an insufficient balance
You can't buy a ticket
Impossible, there should be two million in there
Hey, what happened to the money in my account
Where is my two million
Did you transfer it away
Sir, as this money is in dispute
The sender has requested a reversal
Lewes, you dare play me
Daniel
Where do you think you're going
Trying to run
Brian, I wasn't running
I just stepped out for a bit
Damn it
After him
Damn, get everyone out there
Scour every inch of Verdant Town
Find him and drag him back to me